Glenbert Garing

Makati City, Metro Manila 09564661113 emcee.garing@gmail.com

Summary

An exemplary IT professional with 3 years of experience in Development and Release Management who implements the use of pipelines in creating impressive and effective way in continuous deployment and delivery. Nurtured his skills further through the trainings he attended and has proven to be responsible in all aspects of his work.

Education

Batangas State University

Bachelor's Degree in Information Technology

Batangas, Calabarzon Graduated April 2015

Employment History

Bayview Technologies Incorporated

Linux Release Engineer

Makati, Metro Manila August 2017 - Present

Responsibilities:

Maintain and enhance existing deployment process to move towards continuous delivery

Provide technical support throughout the release process, including known errors and workarounds

Work closely with Devs and QA on Release Engineering process to support continuous growth

Respond constantly and aggressively to automated tests and build issues

Participate on Incident and Problem Management incidents

Monitor incidents and problems, and undertake problem management during deployment, raising bugs as required Provide on-call support to the business to meet their needs

Bayview Technologies Incorporated

Junior Release Engineer

Makati, Metro Manila April 2016 - August 2017

Responsibilities:

Software build and releases

Tests the final delivery prior to QA testing

Provide feedback on the effectiveness of the release

Ability to write technical documentations efficiently

Ability to effectively prioritize and execute task in a high-pressure environment

Participate in Production emergency hot fixes and deployments

Aruze Gaming Philippines Incoporated

C++ Programmer

Responsibilities:

Develop and deploy casino games software

Provide peer-to-peer review to production candidate releases

Involvement on oneself to project kickoffs and schedule management

Create documentations on software errors

Professional Skills

Santo Tomas, Calabarzon May 2015 - January 2016 Python Competent
Gitlab Intermediate
Docker Beginner
Kubernetes Beginner
Ansible Tower Advanced
Artifactory Competent

Languages

English Proficient Filipino Native

References

Krystel Mae Penoso (09176888027)

Colleague

Bayview Technologies Incorporated Makati City, Philippines

Francis Paolo Cruz (09054011275)

Colleague

Bayview Technologies Incorporated Makati City, Philippines